Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 767
    - Local 767 Incoming Correspondence, March 9, 1942-June 30, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Emspak to Russel Painter Regarding Finances, April 13-23, 1943; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Haser Regarding Constitution, October 27, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Virgil Maxwell Regarding Fee Waiver, April 10, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Haser Regarding Fee Waiver, May 1, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Maxwell Regarding Dues, June 7, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Haser Regarding Dues, November 20, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to William Jones Regarding Finances, July 24, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to William McGovern Regarding Waiver, Decmber 27, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to T. Forsythe Regarding Fee, January 26, 1949; 12.
      - Emspak to Forsythe Regarding Materials, March 3, 1949; 13.
      - Emspak to E. Luster Regarding Materials, March 3, 1949; 14.
      - Emspak to Lem Markland Regarding Appeals, May 2, 1949; 15.
      - Emspak to Luster Regarding Motion, June 30, 1949; 16.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to McGovern Regarding Acknowledged Letter, April 7, 1949; 17.
      - James Matles to Glen Hansen Regarding Staff Assignments, March 9, 1942; 18.
      - David Ratner to McGovern Regarding Audit, April 27, 1947; 19.
    - Local 767 Outgoing Correspondence, March 9, 1942-June 30, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Elmer Bresock to Julius Emspak Regarding Materials, March 28, 1942; 1.
      - Bresock to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 24, 1942; 2.
      - Paul Coffey to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, December 5, 1945; 3.
      - William Clark to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Constitution, August 31, 1949; 4.
      - Clark to Emspak Regarding Meeting, August 31, 1949; 5.
      - Executive Board to Russ Nixon Regarding Dispute, April 22, 1944; 6.
      - T. Forsythe to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 11, 1948; 7.
      - Forsythe to Emspak Regarding Fees, January 18, 1949; 8.
      - Forsythe to Emspak Regarding Materials, February 22, 1949; 9.
      - Glenn Hansen to James Matles Regarding Organizational Work, February 16, 1942; 10.
      - Dorothy Haser to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 16, 1942; 11.
      - Haser to Emspak Regarding Constitution, September 20, 1942; 12.
      - Haser to Fitzgerald Regarding Officer List, February 15, 1943; 13.
      - Haser to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 3, 1943; 14.
      - Haser to Emspak Regarding Constitution, October 8, 1944; 15.
      - Haser to Emspak Regarding Procedures, October 14, 1944; 16.
      - Haser to Emspak Regarding Fees, April 23-November 12, 1945; 17-18.
      - William Jones to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 15, 1946; 19.
      - E. Luster to Emspak Regarding Waiver, June 16, 1949; 20.
      - George Mason to Emspak Regarding Case, April 15, 1949; 21.
      - Virgil Maxwell to UE Regarding Finances, April 16, 1945; 22.
      - Maxwell to Emspak Regarding Dues, June 4, 1945; 23.
      - Maxwell to UE Regarding Mailing, August 23, 1945; 24.
      - Maxwell to Emspak Regarding Materials, February 26, 1947; 25.
    - Local 767 Outgoing Correspondence, April 11, 1943-April 4, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - W. McGovern to Dave Ratner Regarding Audit, April 23, 1948; 1.
      - McGovern to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, December 10, 1948; 2.
      - McGovern to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, April 4, 1949; 3.
      - McGovern to Emspak Regarding Voting, 4.
      - McGovern to Emspak Regarding Delegation, 5.
      - McGovern to Fitzgerald Regarding Voting, 6.
      - McGovern to Fitzgerald Regarding Delegation, 7.
      - Russell Pinter to Emspak Regarding Organization, April 15, 1943; 8.
      - Pinter to Emspak Regarding Procedures, 9.
      - Russell Pollock to Neil Brant Regarding Strike, April 11, 1943; 10.
      - Pollock to Brant Regarding Case, April 15, 1943; 11.
      - Marlan Withers to Emspak Regarding Charter, May 19, 1947; 12.
      - Withers to Emspak Regarding Constitution, April 15, 1949; 13.
    - Local 767 Glen Helen Yellow Spring, January 21, 1965-January 31, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Local 767 Bonding, March 23-25, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Local 767 War Labor Board Bonus, November 6, 1942-April 23, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - James Matles to Richard Niebur, November 6, 1942; 1.
      - Nieber to David Scribner, November 1842; 2.
      - Scribner to Niebur, November 13, 1942; 3.
      - Nieber to Matles, April 23, 1943; 4.
    - Local 767 Per Capita Extension, July 26-29, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Arthur Garfield to Ray Klausner, July 26, 1946; 1.
      - Lem Markland to Julius Emspak, July 29, 1946; 2.
    - Local 767 Line Material Strike, February 23-24, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Report of Strike, February 23, 1947; 1.
      - Paul Dunham to James Matles, February 24, 1947; 2.
    - Local 767 Essex Wire Organization, April 25-May 1, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Julius Emspak to Lem Markland, April 25, 1947; 1.
      - Markland to Ray Klausner, May 1, 1947; 2.
    - Local 767 Initiation Waiver, December 13-17, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Julius Emspak to Lem Markland, December 13, 1948; 1.
      - Markland to Emspak, December 17, 1948; 2.
    - Local 767 Additional Waiver Request, June 20-24, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Julius Emspak to Lem Markland, June 20, 1949; 1.
      - Markland to Emspak, June 24, 1949; 2.
    - Local 767 Inter-union Rivalry, May 5-November 8, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Lem Markland to Julius Emspak, May 5, 1949; 1.
      - Vern Slagle to Albert Fitzgerald, August 31, 1949; 2.
      - Slagle to Emspak, November 8, 1949; 3.
    - Local 767 Taft-Hartley Affidavits, November 30-December 9, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Vern Slagle to Julius Emspak, November 30, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to Slagle, December 2, 1949; 2.
      - Slagle to Dave Scribner, December 6, 1949; 3.
      - Scribner to Slagle, December 9, 1949; 4.
    - Local 767 Charter Application and Correspondence, December 10, 1941-February 23, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Charter Application, December 10, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Niebur Regarding Per Capita, March 19, 1943; 2.
      - Ray Klausner to Henry Fiering Regarding Per Capita, April 23, 1945; 3.
      - Lem Markland to Secretary of Labor Regarding Strikes, February 23, 1946; 4.
  - Local 768
    - Local 768 Officers List, February 25, 1944-April 20, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Local 768 Constitution, December 22, 1942-January 28, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Local 768 Resolutions, December 19, 1944-January 3, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Local 768 Membership List, November 3, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Local 768 Membership Resolutions (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Local 768 K.M. Kirkendall Incoming Correspondence, February 10, 1942-December 30, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      - Sanford Bennett Regarding Labor Case, November 18, 1944; 1.
      - Alvin Biscoe Regarding Labor Case, October 19, 1942; 2.
      - Neil Brant Regarding Labor Case, December 2, 1942, January 4, 1943; 3-4.
      - William Cahn Regarding Publications, December 9, 1947; 5.
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, December 30, 1947; 6.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Charter, February 10, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Grievances, March 11, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Local Case, August 20, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 9, 1942-January 20, 1943; 10-11.
      - Emspak Regarding Delegation, March 31, 1943; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Cases, April 4, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Materials, April 21, 1943; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Local Organization, May 20, 1943; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Materials, May 26, 1943; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, August 9, 1943; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Contracts, March 6, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Reports, June 15, 1944; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 16, 1944; 20.
      - Emspak Regarding Materials, July 24, 1944; 21.
      - Emspak Regarding Meeting, August 28, 1944; 22.
      - Emspak Regarding Waiver, January 14, 1946; 23.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, September 16, 1944; 24.
      - Emspak Regarding Materials, April 21, 1947; 25.
    - Local 768 K.M. Kirkendall Incoming Correspondence, February 5, 1942-October 20, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 16-August 16, 1948; 1-3.
      - Emspak Regarding Union Case, October 20, 1949; 4.
      - Herbret Hirshberg Regarding Finances, June 28, 1948; 5.
      - Ray Klausner Regarding Travel Plans, December 8, 1947; 6.
      - Frederick Livingston Regarding Finances, January 9, 1945; 7.
      - James Matles Regarding Staff Assignments, February 5, 1942; 8.
      - Matles Regarding War Production, February 13, 1942; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Recieved Information, May 12, 1942; 10.
      - Matles Regarding Contract, May 29, 1942; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 22, 1942; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Wages, June 29, 1942; 13.
      - Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 30, 1942; 14.
      - Matles Regarding Board Action, December 7, 1942; 15.
      - Matles Regarding Acknowledged Information, December 21, 1942; 16.
      - Matles Regarding Conference, December 30, 1942; 17.
      - Matles Regarding Wages, January 14, 1943; 18.
      - Matles Regarding Recieved Informaiton, January 25, 1943; 19.
      - Matles Regarding Executive Orders, January 25, 1943; 20.
      - Matles Regarding Meeting, 21.
      - Russ Nixon Regarding Requested Information, May 19, 1942; 22.
      - Nixon Regarding Forwarded Letter, June 11, 1942; 23.
      - D. Russell Regarding Contract, January 27, 1943; 24.
      - David Scribner Regarding Contract Procedures, August 20, 1945; 25.
      - Scribner Regarding Given Informaiton, December 14, 1945; 26.
      - Scribner Regarding Union Case, January 18, 1946; 27.
      - Scribner Regarding Procedures, July 17, 1947; 28.
    - Local 768 K.M. Kirkendall Outgoing Correspondence, January 29, 1942-January 7, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 113)
      - K. Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Amalgamation, January 29, 1942; 1.
      - Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter, February 6-10, 1942; 2-3.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, February 11, 1942; 4.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Labor Case, February 27, 1942; 5.
      - Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Staff Recommendations, March 6, 1942; 6.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Contract, March 27, 1942; 7.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Negotiations, May 7, 1942; 8.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Wages, June 19, 1942; 9.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 20, 1942; 10.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Materials, August 14, 1942; 11.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, August 26, 1942; 12.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Materials, October 5-November 9,1942; 13-14.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Constitution, November 12, 1942; 15.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Amalgamation, November 16, 1942; 16.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Union Case, November 30, 1942; 17.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Materials, December 7, 1942; 18.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Labor Case, December 12, 1942; 19.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Meeting, December 16, 1942; 20.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Training Programs, December 17, 1942; 21.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Wages, December 22, 1942; 22.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Conference, December 24, 1942; 23.
      - Kirkendall to J. Wishart Regarding Contract, January 5, 1943; 24.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Wages, January 7, 1943; 25.
    - Local 768 K.M. Kirkendall Outgoing Correspondence, January 7, 1943-April 2, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - K. Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Wages, January 7, 1943; 1.
      - Kirkendall to Walter McDonald Regarding Meeting, January 12, 1943; 2.
      - Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Organizational Work, January 16, 1943; 3.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Memorandum, January 26, 1943; 4.
      - Kirkendall to Chrysler Corporation Regarding Contract, January 26, 1943; 5.
      - Kirkendall to D. Russell Regarding Negotiations, January 28, 1943; 6.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Membership, March 8, 1943; 7.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Delegation, March 25, 1943; 8.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Labor Case, April 1, 1943; 9.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Cases, April 6, 1943; 10.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Executive Orders, April 19, 1943; 11.
      - Kirkendall to Chief Steward Regarding Training Program, June 25, 1943; 12.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Wages, July 26, 1943; 13.
      - Kirkendall to Russ Nixon Regarding Agreement, November 6, 1943; 14.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Membership, January 11, 1944; 15.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding War Production, June 9, 1944; 16.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 16, 1944; 17.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 24, 1944; 18.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Staff Affairs, December 6, 1944; 19.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Campaign Work, December 14, 1944; 20.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 28, 1944; 21.
      - Kirkendall to David Scribner Regarding Proposals, August 8, 1945; 22.
      - Kirkendall to Scribner Regarding Staff Change, August 8, 1945; 23.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Mailing, February 22, 1946; 24.
      - Kirkendall to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Meeting, April 2, 1946; 25.
    - Local 768 K.M. Kirkendall Outgoing Correspondence, April 14, 1946-August 12, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 115)
      - K. Kirkendall to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike, April 14, 1946; 1.
      - Kirkendall to David Scribner Regarding Labor Case, June 14, 1946; 2.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Materials, July 29, 1946; 3.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 14, 1947; 4.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, June 6, 1947; 5.
      - Kirkendall to Scribner Regarding Dues, July 7, 1947; 6.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Travel Plans, December 5, 1947; 7.
      - Kirkendall to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, March 10, 1948; 8.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Materials, April 14, 1948; 9.
      - Kirkendall to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, May 5, 1948; 10.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, June 28, 1948; 11.
      - Kirkendall to UE Wage Committee Regarding Finances, June 28, 1948; 12.
      - Kirkendall to Oakie Wornstaff Regarding Dues, March 25, 1949; 13.
      - Kirkendall to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting Report, August 12, 1949; 14.
      - Kirkendall to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, September 20, 1948; 15.
      - Kirkendall to Emspak Regarding Strike, 16.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Contract, 17.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Work Stoppage, 18-19.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Work Schedule, 20.
      - Kirkendall to Matles Regarding Meeting, 21.
    - Local 768 Incoming Correspondence, February 2, 1942-December 11, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Janet Barish to Anne Hill Regarding Finances, December 11, 1950; 1.
      - Bill Cahn to Bebe Ober Regarding Publicity, April 17, 1947; 2.
      - Cahn to Ober Regarding Publications, April 25-December 10, 1947; 3-4.
      - James Divise to Frank Danowski Regarding Finances, May 28, 1948; 5.
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Galligan Regarding Amalgamation, February 2, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to M. Ambrose Regarding Bonding, February 11, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to William Tootle Regarding Bonding, February 11, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to John Good Regarding Acknowledged Letter, August 21, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Arthur Garfield Regarding Requested Information, August 21, 1942; 10.
      - Emspak to Marinell Ambrose Regarding Resolutions, September 24, 1942; 11.
      - Emspak to Good Regarding Staff Affairs, September 24, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Andrew Gad Regarding Union Procedures, January 19, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to Gad Regarding Wages, March 14, 1944; 14.
      - Emspak to Barbara Armstrong Regarding Resolution, January 10, 1944; 15.
      - Emspak to Oscar Armstrong Regarding Resolution, January 10, 1945; 16.
      - Emspak to O. Armstrong Regarding Fee Waiver, January 29, 1945; 17.
      - Emspak to O. Armstrong Regarding Publications, July 9, 1945; 18.
      - Emspak to Cornelius Grottke Regarding Materials, July 11, 1946; 19.
      - Emspak to Ober Regarding Forwarded Information, April 21, 1947; 20.
      - Emspak to Charles Sims Regarding Strike, May 12, 1947; 21.
      - Emspak to Sims Regarding Strike, May 15, 1947; 22.
      - Emspak to Sims Regarding Finances, May 23-June 11, 1947; 23-24.
    - Local 768 Incoming Correspondence, June 26, 1947-August 20, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest Ketzel Regarding Strike, June 26, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Walter Lohman Regarding Strike, June 4, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Lohman Regarding Finances, July 6-22, 1948; 3-5.
      - Emspak to Lohman Regarding Strike, July 25, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Lohman Regarding Finances, July 28, 1948; 7.
      - Emspak to Lohman Regarding Strike, August 23, 1948; 8.
      - Emspak to Lohman Regarding Finances, September 22-October 1, 1948; 9-10.
      - Emspak to Cornelius Grottke Regarding Finances, April 1, 1949; 11.
      - Emspak to Oakie Wornstaff Regarding Mailing, May 2, 1949; 12.
      - Emspak to Elmer Armstrong Regarding Organizational Work, February 17, 1950; 13.
      - Emspak to Delbert Dunn Regarding Bonding, March 28, 1950; 14.
      - Emspak to Floyd Smith Regarding Finances, May 19, 1950; 15.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding Fee Waiver, July 21, 1950; 16.
      - Emspak to Earl Phillips Regarding Finances, August 24, 1950; 17.
      - Emspak to Will Jones Regarding Local Affairs, November 20, 1950; 18.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding Finances, July 25, 1951; 19.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding Strike, June 12, 1952; 20.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding Finances, July 9, 1952; 21.
      - Emspak to Preston Mack Regarding Finances, July 21, 1952; 22.
      - Emspak to Mack Regarding Finances, July 30-August 20, 1952; 23-26.
    - Local 768 Incoming Correspondence, May 22, 1942-October 26, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Julius Emspak to Preston Mack Regarding Finances, August 26-October 10, 1952; 1-8.
      - Emspak to Mack Regarding Acknowledged Letter, December 2, 1952; 9.
      - Emspak to Edward McKinley Regarding Fee Waiver, March 31, 1953; 10.
      - Emspak to Mack Regarding Finances, April 9, 1953; 11.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Bebe Ober Regarding Rally, May 22, 1942; 12.
      - Fitzgerald to Ober Regarding Membership Drive, May 26, 1942; 13.
      - Fitzgerald to Marinell Ambrose Regarding Convention Report, October 6, 1943; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Ambrose Regarding Social Affairs, March 25, 1947; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Earl Phillips Regarding Local Activities, June 6, 1951; 16.
      - Nicolas Kalovdis to Local Members Regarding Greek Maritime Unions, September 27, 1948; 17.
      - James Matles to Ober Regarding Materials, February 10, 1948; 18.
      - Matles to L. Wornstaff Regarding Staff Assignments, October 1, 1949; 19.
      - Matles to Mack Regarding Finances, November 20-December 18, 1954; 20-21.
      - Matles to Mack Regarding Acknowledged Letter, August 14, 1953; 22.
      - Matles to Mack Regarding Finances, September 28, 1953; 23.
      - Matles to Willie Storey Regarding Finances, July 27, 1954; 24.
      - Matles to Edward McKinley Regarding Staff Report, March 8, 1955; 25.
      - Matles to McKinley Regarding Strike Fund, May 2, 1956; 26.
      - Matles to Bill Greene Regarding Union Representation, October 26, 1961; 27.
    - Local 768 Incoming Correspondence, March 16, 1942-March 31, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Albert Olson to William Tootle Regarding Finances, March 16, 1942; 1.
      - David Ratner to Walter Lohman Regarding Bonding, November 19, 1948; 2.
      - Ratner to Lohman Regarding Audit, December 20, 1948; 3.
      - Ratner to Lohman Regarding Travel Plans, January 4-7, 1949; 4-5.
      - Ratner to Margarete Smock Regarding Finances, March 31, 1949; 6.
      - David Scribner to Bebe Ober Regarding Hearing, October 15, 1949; 7.
      - Scribner to Ober Regarding Taft-Hartley, October 28, 1947; 8.
      - A. Townsen to Tootle Regarding Finances, April 14, 1944; 9.
    - Local 768 Outgoing Correspondence, January 28, 1942-January 9, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Marinell Ambrose to James Matles Regarding Amalgamation, January 28, 1942; 1.
      - Ambrose to Julius Emspak Regarding Officer List, February 6, 1942; 2.
      - Ambrose to Harry Jeffery Regarding Hobbs Bill, April 12, 1943; 3.
      - Ambrose to Joseph Stalin Regarding Support, June 5, 1943; 4.
      - Ambrose to Franklin Roosevelt Regarding International Union Solidarity, June 7, 1943; 5.
      - Ambrose to Emspak Regarding Electon, July 1, 1943; 6.
      - Ambrose to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Convention Report, October 4, 1943; 7.
      - Ambrose to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 26-February 7, 1944; 8-9.
      - Ambrose Letter Regarding Social Unity, February 28, 1947; 10.
      - Elmer Armstrong to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, January 9, 1950; 11.
      - Oscar Armstrong to Emspak Regarding Meeting Results, December 26, 1944; 12.
      - O. Armstrong to Emspak Regarding Union Production, January 24, 1945; 13.
      - O. Armstrong to Emspak Regarding Mailing, June 6, 1945; 14.
      - Marrill Bennett to Emspak Regarding Contracts, May 28, 1943; 15.
      - James Divine Letter Regarding Strike Gains, June 17, 1947; 16.
      - E. Dwald to Matles Regarding Election, 17.
      - Andrew Gad to Emspak Regarding Procedures, January 15, 1943; 18.
      - Gad to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 23-April 6, 1943; 19-20.
      - Gad to Emspak Regarding Staff Affairs, March 9, 1944; 21.
      - Gad to Emspak Regarding Strike, May 14, 1946-July 28, 1947; 22-24.
      - Robert Galligen to Matles Regarding Local Organization, 25.
    - Local 768 Outgoing Correspondence, August 19, 1942-September 25, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - John Good Letter Regarding Membership, August 19, 1942; 1.
      - Bill Greene to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, September 25, 1961; 2.
      - Cornelius Grottke to David Rosston Regarding Bonding, July 18, 1945; 3.
      - Grottke to Julius Emspak Regarding Fee Waiver, January 12, 1946; 4.
      - Grottke to Emspak Regarding Material, June 26, 1946; 5.
      - Grottke to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 22, 1946, May 27, 1947; 6-7.
      - Anne Hill to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, December 8, 1950; 8.
      - Hill to Barish Regarding Materials, February 9, 1951; 9.
      - Hill to Barish Regarding Finances, January 2, 1952; 10.
      - Hill to David Ratner, April 10, 1952; 11.
      - Alice Hussoreg to Emspak Regarding Officer List, January 4, 1943; 12.
      - Will Jones to Emspak Regarding Staff Affairs, November 8, 1950; 13.
      - Jones to Barish Regarding Finances, December 15, 1950; 14.
      - Jones to Emspak Regarding Constitution, January 2, 1951; 15.
      - Ernest Ketzel to Convention Committee Regarding Travel Plans, August 20, 1948; 16.
      - Ketzel to Emspak Regarding Executive Board, October 14, 1948; 17.
      - Walter Lohman to Emspak Regarding Strike Aid, May 27, 1948; 18.
      - Lohman to Emspak Regarding Strike, June 4, 1948; 19.
      - Lohman to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 24, 1948; 20.
      - Lohman to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 25, 1948; 21.